<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Documentation</title>
    <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:46:35 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Balsamiq Cloud</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/intro/</guid>
      <description>What Is Balsamiq Cloud? Balsamiq Cloud is a web-based user interface design tool for creating wireframes (sometimes called mockups or low-fidelity prototypes). You can use it to generate digital sketches of your idea or concept for an application or website, to facilitate discussion and understanding before any code is written. The completed wireframes can be used for user testing, clarifying your vision, getting feedback from stakeholders, or getting approval to start development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Balsamiq Mockups 3</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:32:43 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/intro/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Managing Spaces</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/spaces/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/spaces/</guid>
      <description>A Space on Balsamiq Cloud is where your projects live. We have three tiers of Spaces, and we think that once you find the right size, a single Space will be enough for you and your team. While there may be situations where you are invited to someone else&amp;rsquo;s Space to collaborate on a project, or you need a specific number of projects, we expect you&amp;rsquo;ll only have to manage a single Space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Managing Projects</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/projects/</guid>
      <description>In each of your Spaces, you will find a collection of projects that you and your team are working on.
From this page you can create and upload as many projects as your subscription allows. If you have existing Balsamiq (.bmpr) files you can just drag them on to this screen to upload them.
Note: If you were invited to join a Space, it is likely that there will be projects available to you already.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balsamiq Mockups 3 Application Overview</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:44:43 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/overview/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People and Permissions</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/people/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/people/</guid>
      <description>Balsamiq Cloud has four user permission levels: Space Owner, Staff Members, Project Members, and Billing Only Administrators.
Space Owners Space Owners are the admins for the entire Balsamiq Cloud Space. They can:
 Access any project on the Space Create new projects Add Staff and Project Members to any project on the Space Manage the Space and billing information  Note: See Managing Your Space Settings to learn how to transfer Space ownership or add a second Space Owner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Mockups 3 for Jira Cloud</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 15:52:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/intro/</guid>
      <description>This page contains usage instructions for Mockups 3 for Jira Cloud.
Using Jira Server? If you are hosting Jira behind the firewall, please see this article instead. Jira Cloud Administrators: the Mockups 3 for Jira Cloud Admin Guide is for you.
Note: Mockups 3 for Jira Cloud was released January 18, 2016. See our transition guide if you have the older pre-installed version of Mockups for Jira. Balsamiq Mockups 3 for Jira Cloud provides very similar functionality to Balsamiq Mockups 3 for Desktop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Mockups 3 for Confluence Cloud</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 15:52:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/intro/</guid>
      <description>Using Confluence Server? If you are hosting Confluence behind the firewall, please see this article instead. Confluence Cloud Administrators: the Mockups 3 for Confluence Cloud Admin Guide is for you.
Note: Mockups 3 for Confluence Cloud was released April 4, 2016. See our transition guide if you have the older pre-installed version of Mockups for Confluence. Balsamiq Mockups 3 for Confluence Cloud provides very similar functionality to Balsamiq Mockups 3 for Desktop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balsamiq Mockups 3 for Google Drive Overview</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 15:52:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/intro/</guid>
      <description>Overview Balsamiq Mockups 3 for Google Drive provides the same functionality as other Balsamiq Mockups products. The difference is that the files are stored and managed by Google Drive. If you use other Google Drive apps (Google Docs, for example), the file management features should be very familiar to you.
You can easily share your mockups using the built-in features of Google Drive, even if other people don&amp;rsquo;t have the Balsamiq app installed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>myBalsamiq Terms of Use and Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/tos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/tos/</guid>
      <description>Please read this document carefully before accessing or using myBalsamiq.
Introduction English, Not Legalese Most Terms of Service and Privacy Policy documents are unreadable. They are written by lawyers and for lawyers, and in our opinion are not very effective.
Because we believe in establishing long-term relationships with our customers, we decided to use plain English instead, to make our terms as clear as possible.
Please don&amp;rsquo;t forget that we are real people: take a look at our company page to get to know us a little.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with UI Controls</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/controls/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:45:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/controls/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Editor Overview</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/overview/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>myBalsamiq Application Overview</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/intro/</guid>
      <description>myBalsamiq lets you organize your work by project, create mockups collaboratively, review and iterate designs, and even deploy click-through prototypes for testing. See the myBalsamiq documentation index page for all the myBalsamiq documentation.
Application Overview This short video should give you an idea of what you can do with myBalsamiq.
 You can also watch this video on our YouTube channel.
A Note about Roles and Access Many features of myBalsamiq are role-specific.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mockups 3 for Jira Cloud Admin Guide</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/admin-guide-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 15:52:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/admin-guide-cloud/</guid>
      <description>This page contains links to installation, pricing, and licensing information for Mockups 3 for Jira Cloud.
Using Jira Server? If you are hosting Jira behind the firewall, please see this article instead. Usage instructions for the plugin are in the Balsamiq Mockups 3 for Jira Introduction.
Note: Mockups 3 for Jira Cloud was released January 18, 2016. See our transition guide if you have the older pre-installed version of Mockups for Jira.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mockups 3 for Confluence Cloud Admin Guide</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/admin-guide-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 15:52:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/admin-guide-cloud/</guid>
      <description>This page contains links to installation, pricing, and licensing information for Mockups 3 for Confluence Cloud.
Using Confluence Server? If you are hosting Confluence behind the firewall, please see this article instead. Usage instructions for the plugin are in the Introduction to Mockups 3 for Confluence Cloud.
Note: Mockups 3 for Confluence Cloud was released April 4, 2016. See our transition guide if you have the older pre-installed version of Mockups for Confluence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing Balsamiq Mockups 3 for Google Drive</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/installing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 15:52:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/installing/</guid>
      <description>Installation Installing Balsamiq Mockups 3 for Google Drive is the same as installing other Google Drive apps. It can be installed from the Chrome Web Store.
Note: Balsamiq for Google Drive has been updated with our new editor, Balsamiq Wireframes. You can install the new version from this Chrome Web Store page. Once installed, Balsamiq Mockups 3 for Google Drive will be available in your Google Drive &amp;ldquo;New&amp;rdquo; menu.If you are using the Chrome browser, you can also access Balsamiq Mockups 3 for Google Drive from the Chrome Apps tab (open a new tab and type &amp;ldquo;chrome://apps/&amp;ldquo;).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding and Arranging UI Controls</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/adding-controls/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/adding-controls/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>myBalsamiq Home Page (All Projects)</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/home/</guid>
      <description>Your home page is where Staff Members create and navigate to all the projects your team is working on.
Projects are like folders to keep all of your wireframes together based on whatever organization makes sense to you. For example, you could create a single project for a web site design you’re working on, or you could create multiple projects for the web site design to keep parts of your design separate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mockups 3 for Confluence Cloud Transition Guide</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/transition-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 15:52:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/transition-guide/</guid>
      <description>Mockups 3 for Confluence Cloud was released April 4, 2016. The new version has projects, symbols, real time collaboration and lots of other improvements.
 We retired the old version of the plugin in July 2016. If you wish to use our add-on, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to start a 30 day trial and subscribe to Mockups 3 for Confluence Cloud.
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t yet purchased Mockups for Confluence, but have a Cloud instance older than April 4, 2016, you will have the older plugin pre-installed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mockups 3 for Jira Cloud Transition Guide</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/transition-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 15:52:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/transition-guide/</guid>
      <description>Mockups 3 for Jira Cloud was released January 18, 2016. The new version has projects, symbols, real time collaboration and lots of other improvements.
 We retired the old version of the plugin in June 2016. If you wish to use our add-on, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to start a 30 day trial and subscribe to Mockups 3 for Jira Cloud.
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t yet purchased Mockups for Jira, but have a Cloud instance older than January 18, 2016, you will have the older plugin pre-installed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Files in Google Drive</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/drive-files/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 15:52:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/drive-files/</guid>
      <description>A variety of actions are available from the Google Drive file viewer. These actions are available by selecting a file and clicking one of the icons at the top of the file viewer or by right-clicking on the file. The actions available on Balsamiq Mockups files in Google Drive are common across all types of files in Google Drive, so not all of them are described here. For general help on getting around in Google Drive, check out the Google Drive Help Center.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Account Management</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/account-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/account-management/</guid>
      <description>A Balsamiq Cloud account is your ticket to super-fast wireframing. You only need one account as it can belong to as many spaces as you make, or are invited to.
Signing Up for a Balsamiq Cloud Account The first thing you need to do to start working in Balsamiq Cloud is sign up for an account. To get started, head over to https://balsamiq.cloud.
We offer two sign up methods. You can complete our sign up form:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a New Project in Mockups 3 for Confluence Cloud</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/new-project-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 15:52:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/new-project-cloud/</guid>
      <description>Balsamiq Mockups 3 for Confluence Cloud provides very similar functionality to Balsamiq Mockups 3 for Desktop.
The main difference is that the Balsamiq project files are stored and managed as Confluence Cloud attachments.
 Adding a New Project to a Confluence Page Adding a new Balsamiq Mockups project to a wiki page is very similar to adding an image.
Edit the page, position the cursor where you’d like your mockups to be, then click on the Insert menu and select “Balsamiq Mockups” from the list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collaborating with Other Users in Real Time</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/collaborating/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 15:52:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/collaborating/</guid>
      <description>Balsamiq Mockups 3 for Google Drive supports real-time collaboration between users. Just share the Mockups file with your collaborators, then have everyone launch the application on the same file. Everyone&amp;rsquo;s changes will be shared in real-time with all collaborators.
The other connected users will be shown in the top right of the screen. Hovering over their picture shows their email address.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Editing Controls</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/editing-controls/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/editing-controls/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>myBalsamiq Project Page</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/project/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/project/</guid>
      <description>An individual project page holds all the Mockups for a project.
Projects are like folders to keep all of your wireframes together based on whatever organization makes sense to you. For example, you could create a single project for a web site design you’re working on, or you could create multiple projects for the web site design to keep parts of your design separate. How you organize is up to you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balsamiq Mockups 3 Application Overview</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:44:43 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/overview/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balsamiq Mockups 3 Application Overview</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:44:43 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/overview/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balsamiq Mockups 3 Application Overview</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:44:43 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/overview/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharing and Reviewing</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/sharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/sharing/</guid>
      <description>Balsamiq Cloud is designed for collaboration and offers many ways for you to get feedback on your designs. This document outlines a few different ways so that you can pick the right one to fit each situation.
For sharing with collaborators, just have your Space Owner invite them as staff members. Once they’re set up as staff members on your Balsamiq Cloud Space, you can quickly invite them to projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collaborative Editing</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/collaborating/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/collaborating/</guid>
      <description>Balsamiq Cloud is optimized for collaborative work. This document outlines the different ways to interact with your team, while editing a project.
Note: The following features require Edit permissions, see People and Permissions for more details. Collaborating in Real-Time Balsamiq Cloud supports real-time collaboration between users. Once two or more users join the same project, every change will be reflected in real-time with everyone. The toolbar will show users who have joined the project, and the permission level they have.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Images and Assets</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/images/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/images/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>myBalsamiq Access Control Matrix</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/accesscontrolmatrix/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/accesscontrolmatrix/</guid>
      <description>The table below shows the full access control rules matrix for a myBalsamiq site.
This can be helpful to understand &amp;ldquo;who can do what&amp;rdquo; depending on their role.
View the full matrix in a new window.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with UI Controls</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/controls/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:45:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/controls/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with UI Controls</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/controls/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:45:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/controls/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with UI Controls</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/controls/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:45:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/controls/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Symbols</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/symbols/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/symbols/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>myBalsamiq Single Mockup Page</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/mockup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/mockup/</guid>
      <description>The image below is a marked up screenshot showing all the parts and functions on a single Mockup page.

View full size image in a new window &amp;rarr;
You can also watch the Mockup section of our intro video on YouTube for a quick intro to Mockups in myBalsamiq.
Creating Mockups To Create a mockup, select the New Mockup button in the upper right of a project or mockup page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Property Inspector</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/inspector/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:46:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/inspector/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Property Inspector</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/inspector/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:46:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/inspector/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Property Inspector</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/inspector/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:46:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/inspector/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Property Inspector</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/inspector/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:46:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/inspector/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markup</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/markup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/markup/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>myBalsamiq Mockups Editor</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/editor/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/editor/</guid>
      <description>The Mockups editor in myBalsamiq is similar to the editor in other versions. See the Mockups Application Overview and Working with UI Controls for more details.
UI Overview The myBalsamiq editor is made up of four main parts, as shown below: The Menu Bar, the UI Library, the Mockups editor canvas, and the Project Browser.
The Menu Bar The Menu Bar is where you will find menus and icons for performing common actions, as well as the Quick Add box.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Alternates</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/alternates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/alternates/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Alternates</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/alternates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/alternates/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Alternates</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/alternates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/alternates/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Alternates</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/alternates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/alternates/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mockups Application Overview</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/overview/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with UI Controls</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/controls/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/controls/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Property Inspector</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/inspector/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/inspector/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Text</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/text/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/text/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Data Grids / Tables</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/datagrids/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/datagrids/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Icons</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/icons/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/icons/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Images</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/images/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/images/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Markup</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/markup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/markup/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Symbols</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/symbols/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/symbols/</guid>
      <description>Note: myBalsamiq is the only version 2 web application that supports Symbols. Symbols allow you create reusable common elements across different mockups. Other software often refers to this same feature as templates, master pages, custom components, or widgets.
Creating Symbols Symbols in Mockups are simply named groups which have been &amp;ldquo;converted&amp;rdquo; to symbols.
Symbols can be made from existing groups, or from ones you create fresh. The following steps assume you are creating a new group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linking Wireframes Together</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/linking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/linking/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Site Maps</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/sitemaps/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/sitemaps/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Project Info Panel</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/projectinfo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:46:50 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/projectinfo/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Project Info Panel</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/projectinfo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:46:50 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/projectinfo/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Project Info Panel</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/projectinfo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:46:50 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/projectinfo/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Project Info Panel</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/projectinfo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:46:50 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/projectinfo/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keyboard Shortcuts</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/shortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/shortcuts/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linking Mockups Together</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/linking/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/linking/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Skins (Sketch vs. Wireframe)</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/skins/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/skins/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presenting Your Work</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/fullscreen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/fullscreen/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Skins (Sketch vs. Wireframe)</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/skins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 17:03:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/skins/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Skins (Sketch vs. Wireframe)</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/skins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 17:03:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/skins/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Skins (Sketch vs. Wireframe)</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/skins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 17:03:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/skins/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Skins (Sketch vs. Wireframe)</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/skins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 17:03:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/skins/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Assets in myBalsamiq</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/assets/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/assets/</guid>
      <description>myBalsamiq sites provide an assets manager for Site Assets and Project Assets. You can use this as a place to store re-usable images, Mockups, or other files you want to share with your team.
To access the Assets Manager, click the Assets link in the top right of the page. The screenshot below shows what to look for.
1. Site Assets Site Assets are files which will be available for use across all of your projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Text</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/text/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:47:53 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/text/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Text</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/text/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:47:53 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/text/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Text</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/text/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:47:53 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/text/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Text</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/text/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:47:53 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/text/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exporting to PDF or PNG in myBalsamiq</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/exporting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/exporting/</guid>
      <description>Exporting to PDF Unlike the Desktop version, exporting to PDF from myBalsamiq is done outside of the Editor.
To export to PDF in myBalsamiq, go to the Project page for the mockups you want to export and click the arrow next to the Edit button as shown below.
You will see an option listed there to export to PDF. When you select it you will be presented with some options and when you click the &amp;ldquo;Export to PDF&amp;rdquo; button the file will be created for you to download.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Data Grids / Tables</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/datagrids/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:48:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/datagrids/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Data Grids / Tables</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/datagrids/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:48:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/datagrids/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Data Grids / Tables</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/datagrids/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:48:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/datagrids/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Data Grids / Tables</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/datagrids/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:48:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/datagrids/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Full Screen Presentation Mode</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/fullscreen/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/fullscreen/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alternates</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/alternates/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/alternates/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Site, Project and Mockup History in myBalsamiq</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/history/</guid>
      <description>The history functions allow you to view recent activity on the site, on a project, or on a mockup. You’ll notice below the project or mockup name that there’s a single line of text showing you the last update and who made it. The “View History…” text at the end of this line is a link to view the entire history of updates.
The type of events that will be recorded in the history are shown below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Icons</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/icons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:48:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/icons/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Icons</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/icons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:48:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/icons/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Icons</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/icons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:48:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/icons/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Icons</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/icons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:48:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/icons/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Communication in myBalsamiq</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/communication/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/communication/</guid>
      <description>myBalsamiq offers 3 different ways of communicating via the Project Team menu displayed within a project: Skype Chat, Skype Voice Call, and Email.
Group Communication Skype Chat
Launches Skype and starts a chat session with all project members. For Skype integration (chat and voice call), users will have to add their Skype screen name to their user settings.
Skype Voice Call
Starts Skype video chat with your team (Skype multi-person conference works with up to 4 project members).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Images and Assets</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/images/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:57:52 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/images/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Images and Assets</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/images/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:57:52 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/images/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Images and Assets</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/images/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:57:52 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/images/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Images and Assets</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/images/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:57:52 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/images/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>myBalsamiq Prototype View</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/prototypeview/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/prototypeview/</guid>
      <description>The myBalsamiq Prototype View is one of the sharing options available for your project. To generate and access the Prototype View for your project, click on the arrow in the upper right-hand corner of your Project Page.
After clicking the arrow, your browser will be sent to the Prototype View for your project. You&amp;rsquo;ll notice that the address of the Prototype View contains your myBalsamiq URL and a long string of randomized characters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exporting</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/exporting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/exporting/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>myBalsamiq Email Notifications</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/notifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/notifications/</guid>
      <description>myBalsamiq uses email notifications to keep team members updated on changes to a site. Only people that belong to a project who have also confirmed their account after being added to a site will email get the notification. Read on to learn more.
Users Decide When We Should Send an Email Notifications Email notifications are an easy way to make sure your team stays up to date on the project&amp;rsquo;s progress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Markup</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/markup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:58:17 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/markup/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Markup</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/markup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:58:17 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/markup/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Markup</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/markup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:58:17 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/markup/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Markup</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/markup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:58:17 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/markup/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Importing</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/importing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/importing/</guid>
      <description>Importing Wireframes from Another Cloud Project Sometimes you might want to copy or move a wireframe from one project to another. Here is a simple way to do it:
 Open the two projects (each in its own browser tab or window) In the source project, select the wireframe you want to copy or move. Select all the controls from this wireframe (CTRL/CMD+A) and copy the controls (CTRL/CMD+C) In the target project, paste your controls (CTRL/CMD+V) in a newly created wireframe  That’s it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharing Your Work with outside Clients in myBalsamiq</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/sharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/sharing/</guid>
      <description>Since myBalsamiq is all about collaboration, we offer many ways for you to get feedback on your designs.
This document outlines a few different ways, so that you can pick the right one to fit each situation.
For sharing with colleagues: just have your site owner invite them as staff members. Once they&amp;rsquo;re set up as staff members on your myBalsamiq site you can quickly add them to projects via the Project Members menu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Symbols</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/symbols/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:58:34 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/symbols/</guid>
      <description>Balsamiq Mockups supports the concept of Symbols. A Symbol is a group of controls that represents a single piece of functionality. It is often used for parts of the user interface that show up on several screens. Other software sometimes refers to this feature as templates, master pages, custom components, or widgets.
In essence, Symbols let you create reusable common elements that you can use across different mockups.
Creating Symbols There are two ways to create a Symbol, described below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Symbols</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/symbols/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:58:34 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/symbols/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Symbols</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/symbols/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:58:34 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/symbols/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Symbols</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/symbols/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:58:34 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/symbols/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Symbols</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/symbols/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:58:34 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/symbols/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keyboard Shortcuts</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/shortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/shortcuts/</guid>
      <description>Working with Controls  Might not work with...   Selection   Edit the selected control&amp;#39;s text ENTER or F2  &amp;#xF8FF; &amp;#x2691;  --    Add to selection SHIFT+CLICK    Toggle selection CTRL+CLICK Chrome Chrome   Select All CTRL+A Chrome    Deselect All CTRL+SHIFT+A     Ignore control(s) under cursor Hold ALT     Treat/do not treat selection as markup CTRL+SHIFT+K     Size/Position     Resize maintaining aspect ratio Hold SHIFT while resizing with mouse     Move selection along horizontal or vertical axis Hold SHIFT while dragging   Disable snapping during move or resize Hold CTRL     Grow/Increase text or icon size CTRL+]     Shrink/Decrease text or icon size CTRL+[     Nudge selection 1px &amp;uarr;&amp;darr;&amp;larr;&amp;rarr;     Nudge selection 10px SHIFT+&amp;uarr;&amp;darr;&amp;larr;&amp;rarr;     Nudge-Resize selection 1px CTRL+ALT+&amp;uarr;&amp;darr;&amp;larr;&amp;rarr;     Nudge-Resize selection 10px CTRL+ALT+SHIFT+&amp;uarr;&amp;darr;&amp;larr;&amp;rarr;     Auto-Size selection CTRL+ALT+0     Pan the canvas (Hand tool) SPACE BAR+Click and Drag     Bring to front CTRL+SHIFT+&amp;uarr;     Send to back CTRL+SHIFT+&amp;darr;     Bring forward CTRL+&amp;uarr;     Send backward CTRL+&amp;darr;     Duplicate selection ALT+drag     Edit/History     Undo last command CTRL+Z     Redo last command CTRL+Y or CTRL+SHIFT+Z     Cut the selected controls CTRL+X or SHIFT+DELETE     Copy the selected controls CTRL+C or CTRL+INSERT     Paste CTRL+V or SHIFT+INSERT     Paste In Place CTRL+SHIFT+V     Delete the selected controls DELETE or BACKSPACE     Duplicate the selected controls CTRL+D     Lock the selected controls CTRL+2     Unlock all locked controls CTRL+3     Transform the selected controls CTRL+T     Group     Group the selected controls CTRL+G     Ungroup the selected groups CTRL+SHIFT+G     Align     Align selected controls left CTRL+ALT+1     Align selected controls center CTRL+ALT+2     Align selected controls right CTRL+ALT+3     Align selected controls top CTRL+ALT+4     Align selected controls middle CTRL+ALT+5     Align selected controls bottom CTRL+ALT+6     Working with Icons      Navigating the Suggestion List &amp;uarr;&amp;darr;&amp;larr;&amp;rarr;     Using the selected icon ENTER     Closing the Icons Library ESC     Closing the Suggestion List ESC   Grow/Increase icon size CTRL+]     Shrink/Decrease icon size CTRL+[     Working with Text      Start Editing text of the selected control ENTER or F2     Committing the current text ENTER (single-line controls), CTRL+ENTER (multi-line controls) or click anywhere     Ignoring the current edit ESC     Grow/Increase Text Size CTRL+]     Shrink/Decrease Text Size CTRL+[     Text Formatting      italic _text in underscores_     link [text in brackets]     link with a target [text in brackets](mockup_name) or</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Site Maps</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/sitemaps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:59:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/sitemaps/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Site Maps</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/sitemaps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:59:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/sitemaps/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Site Maps</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/sitemaps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:59:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/sitemaps/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Site Maps</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/sitemaps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:59:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/sitemaps/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User Testing Your myBalsamiq Prototypes</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/usertesting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/usertesting/</guid>
      <description>The prototype view of myBalsamiq projects allows you to show your Mockup without all of the surrounding interface of myBalsamiq.
If you&amp;rsquo;ve linked your Mockups together, this can be useful as a click-through prototype, or even for doing usability testing.
The prototype view follows a project&amp;rsquo;s permissions settings, but allows you to share a private URL using a private key. This is useful for testing with remote usability testing services or for giving to people who aren&amp;rsquo;t project members.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exporting Your Mockups</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/exporting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:59:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/exporting/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exporting Your Mockups</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/exporting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:59:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/exporting/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exporting Your Mockups</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/exporting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:59:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/exporting/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exporting Your Mockups</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/exporting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:59:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/exporting/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>myBalsamiq User Settings</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/usersettings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/usersettings/</guid>
      <description>Users can access their user settings by clicking your username in the header bar at the top of the page.
The User Settings page allows individuals to do edit information about themselves. This information is used by the system, as described below.
Your full name
Used to address you.
Your short name
Used to address you in the header and email notifications, and usually is your first name or nickname.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>myBalsamiq Site Settings</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/sitesettings/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product4/sitesettings/</guid>
      <description>Note: the actions described below are available to site owners only. You can access your site settings by clicking the “Settings” link in the header at the top of the page.
The Site Settings page allows the site owner to change information about your company, add and manage staff, manage your payments, and change some administrative settings. Settings for individual projects, such as who can access a project, are available on the Project page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Importing Mockups and Symbols</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/importing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 17:05:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/importing/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Importing Mockups and Symbols</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/importing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 17:05:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/importing/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Importing Mockups and Symbols</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/importing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 17:05:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/importing/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Importing Mockups and Symbols</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/importing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 17:05:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/importing/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linking Mockups Together</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/linking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2015 10:33:47 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/linking/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linking Mockups Together</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/linking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2015 10:33:47 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/linking/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linking Mockups Together</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/linking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2015 10:33:47 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/linking/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linking Mockups Together</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/linking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2015 10:33:47 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/linking/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Full Screen Presentation Mode</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/fullscreen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2015 10:33:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/fullscreen/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Full Screen Presentation Mode</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/fullscreen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2015 10:33:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/fullscreen/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Full Screen Presentation Mode</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/fullscreen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2015 10:33:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/fullscreen/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Full Screen Presentation Mode</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/fullscreen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2015 10:33:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/fullscreen/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autosaving</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/autosave/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2015 10:33:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/autosave/</guid>
      <description>By default, Mockups 3 for Desktop will automatically save any changes you make. This ensures that you will never lose any work.
Mockups 3 for Desktop automatically saves in two places. First, it commits all changes in real time to the internal backup file. Then after a short period of inactivity, Mockups 3 for Desktop will commit the changes to your original project file. This delay should help when you&amp;rsquo;re saving to a networked drive or folder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Local Storage Folder and Backups</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/localstore/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2015 10:33:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/localstore/</guid>
      <description>The Local Store Folder Balsamiq Mockups 3 for Desktop creates a folder on your hard drive for storing some local data and preferences. It looks something like this:
The easiest way to find it is by opening the &amp;ldquo;About&amp;rdquo; dialog and clicking on the &amp;ldquo;Open Local Store Folder&amp;rdquo; link.
​
For reference, here is the location of this folder on the various operating systems that Balsamiq Mockups for Desktop runs on:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharing in Balsamiq Mockups 3 for Desktop</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/sharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2015 10:33:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/sharing/</guid>
      <description>Collaboration is the foundation of Mockups. From working with your clients and customers, to collaborating with your designers and programmers, Mockups was built with collaboration at its core. Here are the ways you can share your projects.
Share Mockups Project Files A great way to share your work is to send your Mockups project files (files with a .bmpr extension) directly to your clients and collaborators. Just be sure to include a link to download Balsamiq Mockups - https://balsamiq.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balsamiq Mockups 3 Transition Guide</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/transition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:41:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/transition/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test for SS site</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/test_ss/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2018 15:06:03 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/test_ss/</guid>
      <description>HI! This is a Test This is some random content</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keyboard Shortcuts</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/shortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2015 10:34:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/shortcuts/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keyboard Shortcuts</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/shortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2015 10:34:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/b3/shortcuts/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keyboard Shortcuts</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/shortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2015 10:34:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/mockups3/shortcuts/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keyboard Shortcuts</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/shortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2015 10:34:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/mockups3/shortcuts/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test 2</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/test_ss2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/test_ss2/</guid>
      <description>This is test 2 Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Sed commodo, justo vel posuere fringilla, nulla augue eleifend leo, a interdum quam nibh quis orci. Mauris vitae augue vel ipsum faucibus accumsan non sed tellus. Aliquam arcu orci, scelerisque vitae augue vitae, fermentum interdum felis. Suspendisse facilisis diam nisl, nec imperdiet erat dictum a. Aliquam sit amet sollicitudin est. Morbi quis purus a sapien pharetra tempus non id lacus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balsamiq Cloud Terms of Use and Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/tos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product1/tos/</guid>
      <description>Please read this document carefully before accessing or using Balsamiq Cloud.
Introduction English, Not Legalese Most Terms of Use and Privacy Policy documents are unreadable. They are written by lawyers and for lawyers, and in our opinion are not very effective.
Because we believe in establishing long-term relationships with our customers, we decided to use plain English instead as much as possible, to make our terms as clear as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balsamiq Mockups 3 for Desktop System Requirements and Updating</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/systemrequirements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product2/systemrequirements/</guid>
      <description>Balsamiq Mockups 3 for Desktop requires Adobe Air 2.6 to run, which works fine on most computers and Operating Systems. You can find the most recent system requirements for Adobe Air here.
The last time we checked, they were:
Windows  2.33GHz or faster x86-compatible processor, or Intel Atom™ 1.6GHz or faster processor for netbook class devices Microsoft® Windows Server 2008, Windows 7, Windows 8 Classic or Windows 10 512MB of RAM (1GB recommended) AIR SDK Development Supports Microsoft® Windows 7 and above, 64-bit only  Mac  Intel® Core™ Duo 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Mockups 2 for Jira Server</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/mockups2/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 15:52:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/mockups2/intro/</guid>
      <description>This page contains usage instructions for Mockups 2 for Jira Server.
Using Jira Cloud? If you are using Jira Cloud (on atlassian.net), please see this article instead. Jira Administrators: the Mockups for Jira Server Admin Guide is for you.
Adding a UI Mockup to a Jira Issue To add a UI Mockup to a particular Jira issue you simply click on the “Add/Edit UI Mockup to this issue” link:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Mockups 2 for Confluence Server</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/mockups2/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 15:52:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/mockups2/intro/</guid>
      <description>Welcome This page contains usage instructions for Mockups for Confluence Server.
Using Confluence Cloud? If you are using Confluence Cloud (on atlassian.net), please see this article instead. Confluence Server Administrators: the Mockups for Confluence Server Admin Guide is for you.
Creating a New Mockup Adding a mockup to a wiki page is very similar to adding an image.
Edit the page, position the cursor where you&amp;rsquo;d like your mockup to be, then click on the Insert menu and select &amp;ldquo;UI Mockup&amp;rdquo; from the list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mockups 2 for Jira Server Admin Guide</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/mockups2/admin-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 15:52:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/mockups2/admin-guide/</guid>
      <description>This page contains installation, registration, updating and uninstalling instructions for Mockups 2 for Jira Server when installed on your own server.
Using Jira Cloud? If you are using Jira Cloud (on atlassian.net), please see this article instead. Usage instructions for the plugin are in the Mockups for Jira Server Introduction.
Installation Instructions Like most Atlassian add-ons, Balsamiq Mockups for Jira is installed via Atlassian&amp;rsquo;s Universal Plugin Manager, or UPM. Make sure you are running an updated version of UPM before attempting to install the plugin (UPM installation instructions).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mockups 2 for Confluence Server Admin Guide</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/mockups2/admin-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 15:52:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/mockups2/admin-guide/</guid>
      <description>Welcome The Mockups 2 for Confluence Server Admin Guide contains installation, registration, updating and uninstalling instructions for Mockups for Confluence Server when installed on your own server.
Using Confluence Cloud? If you are using Confluence Cloud (on atlassian.net), please see this article instead. Usage instructions for the plugin are here.
Installation Instructions Like most plugins, Balsamiq Mockups for Confluence Server is installed via Atlassian&amp;rsquo;s Universal Plugin Manager, or UPM. Make sure you are running an updated version of UPM before attempting to install the plugin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mockups Application Overview</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/mockups2/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/mockups2/overview/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mockups Application Overview</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/mockups2/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/mockups2/overview/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with UI Controls</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/mockups2/controls/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/mockups2/controls/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Property Inspector</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/mockups2/inspector/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/mockups2/inspector/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with UI Controls</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/mockups2/controls/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/mockups2/controls/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Skins (Sketch vs. Wireframe)</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/mockups2/skins/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/mockups2/skins/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Property Inspector</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/mockups2/inspector/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/mockups2/inspector/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Text</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/mockups2/text/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/mockups2/text/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Data Grids / Tables</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/mockups2/datagrids/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/mockups2/datagrids/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Skins (Sketch vs. Wireframe)</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/mockups2/skins/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/mockups2/skins/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Icons</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/mockups2/icons/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/mockups2/icons/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Text</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/mockups2/text/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/mockups2/text/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Data Grids / Tables</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/mockups2/datagrids/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/mockups2/datagrids/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Images</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/mockups2/images/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/mockups2/images/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Icons</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/mockups2/icons/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/mockups2/icons/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Markup</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/mockups2/markup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/mockups2/markup/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Images</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/mockups2/images/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/mockups2/images/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Site Maps</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/mockups2/sitemaps/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/mockups2/sitemaps/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linking Mockups Together</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/mockups2/linking/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/mockups2/linking/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Markup</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/mockups2/markup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/mockups2/markup/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Site Maps</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/mockups2/sitemaps/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/mockups2/sitemaps/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linking Mockups Together</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/mockups2/linking/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/mockups2/linking/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presenting Your Work</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/mockups2/fullscreen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/mockups2/fullscreen/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presenting Your Work</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/mockups2/fullscreen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/mockups2/fullscreen/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keyboard Shortcuts</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/mockups2/shortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/mockups2/shortcuts/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keyboard Shortcuts</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/mockups2/shortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 15:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/mockups2/shortcuts/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Balsamiq Wireframes for Confluence Cloud</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/wireframes/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/wireframes/intro/</guid>
      <description>Using Confluence Server? If you are hosting Confluence behind the firewall, please see this article instead. Confluence Cloud Administrators: the Balsamiq Wireframes for Confluence Cloud Admin Guide is for you.
Balsamiq Wireframes for Confluence Cloud provides very similar functionality to Balsamiq Mockups 3 for Desktop.
The main difference is that the Balsamiq project files are stored and managed as Confluence Cloud attachments.
 Adding a New Project to a Confluence Page Adding a new Balsamiq Wireframes project to a wiki page is very similar to adding an image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Balsamiq Wireframes for Confluence Server</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/wireframes/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 15:52:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/wireframes/intro/</guid>
      <description>This page contains usage instructions for Balsamiq Wireframes for Confluence Server.
Using Confluence Cloud? Please see this article instead. Confluence Server Administrators: the Balsamiq Wireframes for Confluence Server Admin Guide is for you.
Note: Balsamiq Wireframes for Confluence Server was released on September 2017. See our transition guide if you have a previous version of our Confluence add-on installed. Balsamiq Wireframes for Confluence Server provides very similar functionality to Balsamiq Mockups 3 for Desktop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Balsamiq Wireframes for Jira Cloud</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/wireframes/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 15:52:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/wireframes/intro/</guid>
      <description>This page contains usage instructions for Balsamiq Wireframes for Jira Cloud.
Using Jira Server? Please see this article instead. Jira Cloud Administrators: the Balsamiq Wireframes for Jira Cloud Admin Guide is for you.
Balsamiq Wireframes for Jira Cloud provides very similar functionality to Balsamiq Mockups 3 for Desktop. The main difference is that the Balsamiq project files are stored and managed as Jira Cloud attachments.
 Adding a New Project to a Jira Issue To add a new Balsamiq Wireframes project to a particular Jira issue, you simply need to click on the &amp;ldquo;Add Balsamiq Wireframes&amp;rdquo; link.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Balsamiq Wireframes for Jira Server</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/wireframes/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 15:52:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/wireframes/intro/</guid>
      <description>This page contains usage instructions for Balsamiq Wireframes for Jira Server.
Using Jira Cloud? Please see this article instead. Jira Server Administrators: the Balsamiq Wireframes for Jira Server Admin Guide is for you.
Note: Balsamiq Wireframes for Jira Server was released on September, 2017. See our transition guide if you have the older pre-installed version of wireframes for Jira. Balsamiq Wireframes for Jira Server provides very similar functionality to Balsamiq Mockups 3 for Desktop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balsamiq Wireframes for Confluence Cloud Admin Guide</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/wireframes/admin-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/wireframes/admin-guide/</guid>
      <description>This page contains links to installation, pricing, and licensing information for Balsamiq Wireframes for Confluence Cloud.
Using Confluence Server? If you are hosting Confluence behind the firewall, please see this article instead. Usage instructions for the add-on are in the Introduction to Balsamiq Wireframes for Confluence Cloud.
Balsamiq Wireframes for Confluence Cloud is an Atlassian-Connect powered add-on, sold exclusively via Atlassian Marketplace.
Useful Links  Product Page on Atlassian Marketplace Installation instructions Pricing and Licensing information Confluence Cloud Documentation on Managing Add-Ons  Once installed, the add-on will be available to all of your Confluence users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balsamiq Wireframes for Confluence Server Admin Guide</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/wireframes/admin-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 15:52:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/wireframes/admin-guide/</guid>
      <description>This page contains installation, registration, updating and uninstalling instructions for Balsamiq Wireframes for Confluence Server when installed on your own server.
Note: If you are using confluence Cloud (on atlassian.net), please see this article instead. Usage instructions for the plugin are in the Balsamiq Wireframes for Confluence Server Introduction.
Installation Instructions Like most Atlassian add-ons, Balsamiq Wireframes for Confluence is installed via Atlassian’s Universal Plugin Manager, or UPM.
To install the plugin, go to the Confluence Administration page, select &amp;ldquo;Find new add-ons&amp;rdquo; from the Add-ons panel and search for Balsamiq Wireframes for Confluence Server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balsamiq Wireframes for Jira Cloud Admin Guide</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/wireframes/admin-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 15:52:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/wireframes/admin-guide/</guid>
      <description>This page contains links to installation, pricing, and licensing information for Balsamiq Wireframes for Jira Cloud.
Using Jira Server? If you are hosting Jira behind the firewall, please see this article instead. Usage instructions for the plugin are in the Balsamiq Wireframes for Jira Cloud Introduction.
Balsamiq Wireframes for Jira Cloud is an Atlassian-Connect powered add-on, sold exclusively via Atlassian Marketplace.
Useful Links  Product Page on Atlassian Marketplace Installation instructions Pricing and Licensing information Jira Cloud Documentation on Managing Add-Ons  Once installed, the add-on will be available to all of your Jira users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balsamiq Wireframes for Jira Server Admin Guide</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/wireframes/admin-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 15:52:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/wireframes/admin-guide/</guid>
      <description>This page contains installation, registration, updating and uninstalling instructions for Balsamiq Wireframes for Jira Server when installed on your own server.
Note: If you are using Jira Cloud (on atlassian.net), please see this article instead. Usage instructions for the plugin are in the Balsamiq Wireframes for Jira Server Introduction.
Installation Instructions Like most Atlassian add-ons, Balsamiq Wireframes for Jira is installed via Atlassian’s Universal Plugin Manager, or UPM.
To install the plugin, go to the Jira Administration page, select &amp;ldquo;Find new add-ons&amp;rdquo; from the Add-ons panel and search for Balsamiq Wireframes for Jira Server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balsamiq Wireframes for Confluence Cloud Transition Guide</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/wireframes/transition-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/wireframes/transition-guide/</guid>
      <description>Note: This transition guide describes the steps to convert BMML files (old format) to BMPR files. Existing BMPR files will work fine in the new version of the add-on. A new major version of the Balsamiq add-on for Confluence Cloud was released on January 2018. The new version has projects, symbols, comments, chat, real time collaboration and lots of other improvements.
Here’s a quick, 5-minute video walkthrough for some of the highlights of Balsamiq Wireframes for Confluence Cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balsamiq Wireframes for Confluence Server Transition Guide</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/wireframes/transition-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 15:52:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/wireframes/transition-guide/</guid>
      <description>Balsamiq Wireframes for Confluence Server was released was released on September 2017. The new version has projects, symbols, comments, chat, real time collaboration and lots of other improvements.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a quick, 5-minute video walkthrough for some of the highlights of Balsamiq Wireframes for Confluence Server.
 A New File Format In the old version of Balsamiq Mockups for Confluence Server, we stored each mockup in its own BMML attachment, and only linked to images.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balsamiq Wireframes for Jira Cloud Transition Guide</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/wireframes/transition-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 15:52:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/wireframes/transition-guide/</guid>
      <description>Note: This transition guide describes the steps to convert BMML files (old format) to BMPR files. Existing BMPR files will work fine in the new version of the add-on. A new major version of the Balsamiq add-on for Jira Cloud was released on January 2018. The new version has projects, symbols, comments, chat, real time collaboration and lots of other improvements.
Here’s a quick, 5-minute video walkthrough for some of the highlights of Balsamiq Wireframes for Jira Cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balsamiq Wireframes for Jira Server Transition Guide</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/wireframes/transition-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 15:52:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/wireframes/transition-guide/</guid>
      <description>Balsamiq Wireframes for Jira Server was released was released on September, 2017. The new version has projects, symbols, comments, chat, real time collaboration and lots of other improvements.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a quick, 5-minute video walkthrough for some of the highlights of Balsamiq Wireframes for Jira Server.
 A New File Format In the old version of Balsamiq Mockups for Jira Server, we stored each mockup in its own BMML attachment, and only linked to images.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Real-Time Collaboration Service Troubleshooting</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/wireframes/rtc-troubleshooting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 15:52:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/wireframes/rtc-troubleshooting/</guid>
      <description>Balsamiq Wireframes for Jira Server uses a &amp;ldquo;behind the firewall&amp;rdquo; service in order to allow real time collaboration, chat and other features. To verify that the service works as intended, you can use the configuration page of the add-on.
This should be the expected status.
In case of problem, the config page will show an error status.
In case the status of the Real-Time Collaboration Service is DOWN, you should verify that:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Real-Time Collaboration Service Troubleshooting</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/wireframes/rtc-troubleshooting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 15:52:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/wireframes/rtc-troubleshooting/</guid>
      <description>Balsamiq Wireframes for Confluence Server uses a &amp;ldquo;behind the firewall&amp;rdquo; service in order to allow real time collaboration, chat and other features. To verify that the service works as intended, you can use the configuration page of the add-on.
This should be the expected status.
In case of problem, the config page will show an error status.
In case the status of the Real-Time Collaboration Service is DOWN, you should verify that:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balsamiq Wireframes for Google Drive Overview</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/product3v1_1/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/product3v1_1/intro/</guid>
      <description>Overview Balsamiq Wireframes for Google Drive allows you to add and edit wireframes directly from Google Drive, where the files are stored and managed. If you use other Google Drive apps (Google Docs, for example), the file management features should be very familiar to you.
With easy sharing, version control and even real-time collaboration, Balsamiq Wireframes for Google Drive makes iterating on wireframes easy and fun. To learn how to sign up for or manage a subscription, check out the Balsamiq Wireframes for Google Drive subscription FAQ.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing Balsamiq Wireframes for Google Drive</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/product3v1_1/installing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/product3v1_1/installing/</guid>
      <description>Installation Installing Balsamiq Wireframes for Google Drive is the same as installing other Google Drive apps. It can be installed from the Chrome Web Store here.
Permissions During the installation process, the app will ask for the following permissions:
 View metadata for files in your Google Drive is needed to access a project&amp;rsquo;s containing folder (for our breadcrumb link).
 View your Google Drive apps is needed to know if the app is the default one associated to the BMPR file format and to check if an older version of the app is installed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balsamiq Wireframes for Google Drive Transition Guide</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/product3v1_1/transition/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/product3v1_1/transition/</guid>
      <description>Balsamiq Wireframes for Google Drive was released in September, 2017. The new version has a brand new editor (no more Flash needed!), comments, chat and lots of other improvements.
Here’s a quick, 5-minute video walkthrough for some of the highlights of Balsamiq Wireframes for Google Drive.
 The transition to our new app for Google Drive should be smooth, but please don’t hesitate to contact us if you have any trouble, we&amp;rsquo;re here to help!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balsamiq Wireframes Integration With G Suite</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/product3v1_1/gsuite/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/product3v1_1/gsuite/</guid>
      <description>Balsamiq Wireframes for Google Drive is fully integrated with G Suite apps (Docs, Sheets, Slides).
The free Balsamiq Wireframes add-ons allow you to quickly browse and insert your wireframes in your G Suite documents. Take a look at how quick it is!
Once Balsamiq Wireframes for Google Drive is installed, you can download these add-ons for free here:
 Balsamiq Wireframes for Google Docs Balsamiq Wireframes for Google Sheets Balsamiq Wireframes for Google Slides  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Files in Google Drive</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/product3v1_1/drive-files/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/product3v1_1/drive-files/</guid>
      <description>A variety of actions are available from the Google Drive file viewer, by selecting a file and clicking one of the icons in the Google Drive toolbar or by right-clicking on the file.
Note: These actions are common to all types of files in Google Drive, so not all of them are described here. For general help on getting around in Google Drive, check out the Google Drive Help Center.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Real-Time Collaboration Service Configuration</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/wireframes/rtcconfigs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 15:52:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/wireframes/rtcconfigs/</guid>
      <description>Our Atlassian server add-ons include a built-in, behind the firewall real-time collaboration service (RTC) that allows multiple users to work on the same project, at the same time. This documentation is to help administrators understand how the service is implemented, and potentially help them solve problems with it.
It&amp;rsquo;s a service on the main application server that needs to be configured according to the existing network layout. Except for common setups (direct connection to tomcat), you need administration access to the server console to edit reverse proxy configuration files or open the desired port.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Real-Time Collaboration Service Configuration</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/wireframes/rtcconfigs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 15:52:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/wireframes/rtcconfigs/</guid>
      <description>Our Atlassian server add-ons include a built-in, behind the firewall real-time collaboration service (RTC) that allows multiple users to work on the same project, at the same time. This documentation is to help administrators understand how the service is implemented, and potentially help them solve problems with it.
It&amp;rsquo;s a service on the main application server that needs to be configured according to the existing network layout. Except for common setups (direct connection to tomcat), you need administration access to the server console to edit reverse proxy configuration files or open the desired port.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Editor Overview</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/product3v1_1/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/product3v1_1/overview/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Editor Overview</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/wireframes/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/wireframes/overview/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Editor Overview</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/wireframes/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/wireframes/overview/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Editor Overview</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/wireframes/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/wireframes/overview/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Editor Overview</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/wireframes/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/wireframes/overview/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding and Arranging UI Controls</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/product3v1_1/adding-controls/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/product3v1_1/adding-controls/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding and Arranging UI Controls</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/wireframes/adding-controls/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/wireframes/adding-controls/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding and Arranging UI Controls</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/wireframes/adding-controls/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/wireframes/adding-controls/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding and Arranging UI Controls</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/wireframes/adding-controls/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/wireframes/adding-controls/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding and Arranging UI Controls</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/wireframes/adding-controls/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/wireframes/adding-controls/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Editing UI Controls</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/product3v1_1/editing-controls/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/product3v1_1/editing-controls/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Editing UI Controls</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/wireframes/editing-controls/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/wireframes/editing-controls/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Editing UI Controls</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/wireframes/editing-controls/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/wireframes/editing-controls/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Editing UI Controls</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/wireframes/editing-controls/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/wireframes/editing-controls/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Editing UI Controls</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/wireframes/editing-controls/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/wireframes/editing-controls/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharing and Reviewing</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/product3v1_1/sharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/product3v1_1/sharing/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharing and Reviewing</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/wireframes/sharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/wireframes/sharing/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharing and Reviewing</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/wireframes/sharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/wireframes/sharing/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharing and Reviewing</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/wireframes/sharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/wireframes/sharing/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharing and Reviewing</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/wireframes/sharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/wireframes/sharing/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collaborative Editing</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/product3v1_1/collaborating/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/product3v1_1/collaborating/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collaborative Editing</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/wireframes/collaborating/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/wireframes/collaborating/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collaborative Editing</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/wireframes/collaborating/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/wireframes/collaborating/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collaborative Editing</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/wireframes/collaborating/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/wireframes/collaborating/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collaborative Editing</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/wireframes/collaborating/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/wireframes/collaborating/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Images, Assets, and Icons</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/product3v1_1/images/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/product3v1_1/images/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Images, Assets, and Icons</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/wireframes/images/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/wireframes/images/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Images, Assets, and Icons</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/wireframes/images/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/wireframes/images/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Images, Assets, and Icons</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/wireframes/images/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/wireframes/images/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Images, Assets, and Icons</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/wireframes/images/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/wireframes/images/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Symbols</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/product3v1_1/symbols/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/product3v1_1/symbols/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Symbols</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/wireframes/symbols/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/wireframes/symbols/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Symbols</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/wireframes/symbols/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/wireframes/symbols/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Symbols</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/wireframes/symbols/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/wireframes/symbols/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Symbols</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/wireframes/symbols/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/wireframes/symbols/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markup</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/product3v1_1/markup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/product3v1_1/markup/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markup</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/wireframes/markup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/wireframes/markup/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markup</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/wireframes/markup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/wireframes/markup/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markup</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/wireframes/markup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/wireframes/markup/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markup</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/wireframes/markup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/wireframes/markup/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linking Wireframes Together</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/product3v1_1/linking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/product3v1_1/linking/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linking Wireframes Together</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/wireframes/linking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/wireframes/linking/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linking Wireframes Together</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/wireframes/linking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/wireframes/linking/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linking Wireframes Together</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/wireframes/linking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/wireframes/linking/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linking Wireframes Together</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/wireframes/linking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/wireframes/linking/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Full Screen Presentation Mode</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/product3v1_1/fullscreen/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/product3v1_1/fullscreen/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Full Screen Presentation Mode</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/wireframes/fullscreen/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/wireframes/fullscreen/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Full Screen Presentation Mode</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/wireframes/fullscreen/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/wireframes/fullscreen/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Full Screen Presentation Mode</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/wireframes/fullscreen/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/wireframes/fullscreen/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Full Screen Presentation Mode</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/wireframes/fullscreen/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/wireframes/fullscreen/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alternates</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/product3v1_1/alternates/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/product3v1_1/alternates/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alternates</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/wireframes/alternates/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/wireframes/alternates/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alternates</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/wireframes/alternates/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/wireframes/alternates/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alternates</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/wireframes/alternates/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/wireframes/alternates/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alternates</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/wireframes/alternates/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/wireframes/alternates/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exporting</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/product3v1_1/exporting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/product3v1_1/exporting/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exporting</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/wireframes/exporting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/wireframes/exporting/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exporting</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/wireframes/exporting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/wireframes/exporting/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exporting</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/wireframes/exporting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/wireframes/exporting/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exporting</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/wireframes/exporting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/wireframes/exporting/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Importing</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/product3v1_1/importing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/product3v1_1/importing/</guid>
      <description>Importing Wireframes from Another Project Sometimes you might want to copy or move a wireframe from one project to another. Here is a simple way to do it:
 Open the two projects (each in its own browser tab or window) In the source project, select the wireframe you want to copy or move. Select all the controls from this wireframe (CTRL/CMD+A) and copy the controls (CTRL/CMD+C) In the target project, paste your controls (CTRL/CMD+V) in a newly created wireframe  That’s it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Importing</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/wireframes/importing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/wireframes/importing/</guid>
      <description>Importing Wireframes from Another Project Sometimes you might want to copy or move a wireframe from one project to another. Here is a simple way to do it:
 Open the two projects (each in its own browser tab or window) In the source project, select the wireframe you want to copy or move. Select all the controls from this wireframe (CTRL/CMD+A) and copy the controls (CTRL/CMD+C) In the target project, paste your controls (CTRL/CMD+V) in a newly created wireframe  That’s it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Importing</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/wireframes/importing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/wireframes/importing/</guid>
      <description>Importing Wireframes from Another Project Sometimes you might want to copy or move a wireframe from one project to another. Here is a simple way to do it:
 Open the two projects (each in its own browser tab or window) In the source project, select the wireframe you want to copy or move. Select all the controls from this wireframe (CTRL/CMD+A) and copy the controls (CTRL/CMD+C) In the target project, paste your controls (CTRL/CMD+V) in a newly created wireframe  That’s it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Importing</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/wireframes/importing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/wireframes/importing/</guid>
      <description>Importing Wireframes from Another Project Sometimes you might want to copy or move a wireframe from one project to another. Here is a simple way to do it:
 Open the two projects (each in its own browser tab or window) In the source project, select the wireframe you want to copy or move. Select all the controls from this wireframe (CTRL/CMD+A) and copy the controls (CTRL/CMD+C) In the target project, paste your controls (CTRL/CMD+V) in a newly created wireframe  That’s it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Importing</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/wireframes/importing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/wireframes/importing/</guid>
      <description>Importing Wireframes from Another Project Sometimes you might want to copy or move a wireframe from one project to another. Here is a simple way to do it:
 Open the two projects (each in its own browser tab or window) In the source project, select the wireframe you want to copy or move. Select all the controls from this wireframe (CTRL/CMD+A) and copy the controls (CTRL/CMD+C) In the target project, paste your controls (CTRL/CMD+V) in a newly created wireframe  That’s it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keyboard Shortcuts</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/product3v1_1/shortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v1/product3v1_1/shortcuts/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keyboard Shortcuts</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/wireframes/shortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/cloud/wireframes/shortcuts/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keyboard Shortcuts</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/wireframes/shortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v2/server/wireframes/shortcuts/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keyboard Shortcuts</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/wireframes/shortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/cloud/wireframes/shortcuts/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keyboard Shortcuts</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/wireframes/shortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/product3v3/server/wireframes/shortcuts/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balsamiq Cloud Terms of Use and Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/tos/cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/tos/cloud/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>myBalsamiq Terms of Use and Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/tos/mybalsamiq/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:46:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/tos/mybalsamiq/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/search/</guid>
      <description> My HTML Page       My HTML Page    Search              </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding and Arranging UI Controls</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_wireframes/adding-controls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_wireframes/adding-controls/</guid>
      <description>Adding UI Controls To add UI controls to your mockup, double-click or drag a control in the UI Library or type a keyword into the Quick Add tool.
You can also duplicate controls already on the canvas using copy and paste or the duplicate command (CTRL/CMD + D). ALT/Option + drag will also duplicate controls and allow you to place them using your mouse.
Note: Full list of keyboard shortcuts here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alternates</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_wireframes/alternates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_wireframes/alternates/</guid>
      <description>Alternates (also sometimes referred to as versions or branches) allow you to create variations on a single wireframe design without adding more wireframes to your project.
Creating alternates can be useful during the early design phase when exploring concepts and in later stages for reviewers to add their feedback and propose changes.
Some possible reasons for using alternates:
 You want to create only one wireframe per screen but have several ideas about each one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balsamiq Mockups 3 Application Overview</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/overview/</guid>
      <description>Balsamiq Mockups is a user interface design tool for creating wireframes (also called mockups or low-fidelity prototypes). You can use it to generate digital sketches of your product ideas to facilitate discussion and understanding before any code is written.
Each Balsamiq Mockups file (with a .bmpr file extension) represents one project and can contain many mockups and images, which are stored together in a single .bmpr file. Mockups for different projects should be created in separate Balsamiq Mockups files.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balsamiq Mockups 3 Transition Guide</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/transition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/transition/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for trying out our latest version of Balsamiq Mockups! We think that you&amp;rsquo;ll really like all of the improvements and find it easier to use. To learn more about the new features you can read the Introduction to Balsamiq Mockups 3 or dive into our complete documentation.
This article is intended to answer some questions you might have about switching to Balsamiq Mockups 3 from a previous version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collaborative Editing</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_wireframes/collaborating/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_wireframes/collaborating/</guid>
      <description>Balsamiq Wireframes is optimized for collaborative work. This document outlines the different ways to interact with your team, while editing a project.
Collaborating in Real-Time Balsamiq Wireframes supports real-time collaboration between users. Once two or more users join the same project, every change will be reflected in real-time with everyone. The toolbar will show users who have joined the project.
The navigator panel indicates which wireframes your co-workers are working on by displaying their profile picture there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Editing Controls</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_wireframes/editing-controls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_wireframes/editing-controls/</guid>
      <description>Once you&amp;rsquo;ve added controls to the editor canvas you can edit them by typing directly into them and by changing their properties in the properties panel on the right. Both will be described below.
Editing Properties via the Property Inspector The Property Inspector is a panel on the right side of the application that allows you to set some common properties such as alignment, position and size as well as settings specific to certain controls (selection state, text properties, color, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Editor Overview</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_wireframes/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_wireframes/overview/</guid>
      <description>The Balsamiq Wireframes editor interface is made up of five primary areas: the toolbar, the UI Library, the canvas, the navigator panel and the properties panel. Each is described below.
The Toolbar The toolbar contains a series of icons for performing actions on other areas of the user interface.
The first set of icons is described below.
 Show/Hide the left panel View your wireframes as a thumbnail grid Create a new wireframe Wireframe actions (rename, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exporting</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_wireframes/exporting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_wireframes/exporting/</guid>
      <description>The Export menu contains the following export options:
Read on for descriptions of all of the options or skip ahead using the links below.
 Export to PDF Current or All Wireframes to PNG Wireframe to JSON Download Project BMPR  Exporting to PDF You can export the wireframes in your project as a PDF, which can be useful for printing, sending by email, presenting to clients, or posting online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exporting Your Mockups</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/exporting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/exporting/</guid>
      <description>The Export menu contains the following export options:
Read on for descriptions of all of the options or skip ahead using the links below.
 Export to PDF&amp;hellip; Current or All Mockups to PNG Mockup to Clipboard Mockup to JSON Project to BMMLs ZIP&amp;hellip;  Exporting to PDF You can export the mockups in your project as a PDF, which can be useful for printing, sending by email, presenting to clients, or posting online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Full Screen Presentation Mode</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/fullscreen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/fullscreen/</guid>
      <description>Mockups includes a full screen presentation mode for presenting your wireframes to stakeholders or usability testing.
To enter Full Screen Presentation mode, just click on the full-screen icon in the top-right corner of Mockups, or select &amp;ldquo;Full Screen Presentation&amp;rdquo; from the View menu, or simply hit CTRL/CMD+F.
Balsamiq Mockups will expand to take up your whole screen, with your mockup centered on it.
The far left icon toggles the top bar on and off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Full Screen Presentation Mode</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_wireframes/fullscreen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_wireframes/fullscreen/</guid>
      <description>The Full Screen Presentation Mode is great for presenting your wireframes to stakeholders or usability testing.
To enter it, just click on the full-screen icon in the top-right corner of your toolbar, select &amp;ldquo;Full Screen Presentation&amp;rdquo; from the View menu or simply hit CTRL/CMD+F.
The application will expand to take up your whole screen, with your wireframe centered on it.
The far left icon toggles the top bar on and off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Importing</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_wireframes/importing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_wireframes/importing/</guid>
      <description>Do this one later, see if we can adapt it for all versions</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Importing Mockups and Symbols</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/importing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/importing/</guid>
      <description>Importing Mockups from a Previous Version (BMML Files) Balsamiq Mockups 3 uses a different file format from previous versions. You can import your old mockups in one of three formats:
 Individual BMML files A folder containing BMML files (with images and Symbols in an assets sub-folder) A ZIP file containing BMML files (with or without images and Symbols in an assets sub-folder)  To convert your existing project folders or ZIP files into BMPR files, open the Project &amp;gt; Import menu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Balsamiq Mockups 3</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/intro/</guid>
      <description>Balsamiq Mockups 3 is the result of nearly a year of heads-down coding to create the product that our customers have been asking for and the product we wanted for ourselves.
The most noticeable changes are the two &amp;ldquo;biggies&amp;rdquo; that people have asked for since the very beginning: Support for projects (bundled files, multiple windows) and getting rid of that &amp;ldquo;floating property thingy&amp;rdquo; (the property inspector).
But just as important was the work that was done under the hood to make it faster and smarter and the little tweaks across every part of the experience that we hope will make using it even better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keyboard Shortcuts</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b2/shortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b2/shortcuts/</guid>
      <description>Note: Some of these shortcuts do not work in our web versions, depending on which browser and operating system you are using.  Download: PDF | PNG  
Below is a list of all the keyboard shortcuts and modifiers which you can use in Balsamiq Mockups.
Choose one of the links to the right to download a cheat sheet.
  Working with Controls    Selection   Edit the selected control&#39;s text ENTER or F2   Add to selection SHIFT+CLICK   Toggle selection CTRL+CLICK   Select All CTRL+A   Deselect All CTRL+SHIFT+A   Size / Position   Resize maintaining aspect ratio Hold SHIFT   Disable snapping during move or resize Hold CTRL   Increase font or icon size CTRL+]   Decrease font or icon size CTRL+[   Nudge selection 1px ↑↓←→   Nudge selection 20px SHIFT+ ↑↓←→   Nudge-Resize selection 2px CTRL+ALT+ ↑↓←→   Nudge-Resize selection 20px CTRL+ALT+SHIFT+ ↑↓←→   Pan the canvas (Hand tool) SPACE BAR+Click and Drag   Bring to front CTRL+SHIFT+↑   Send to back CTRL+SHIFT+↓   Bring forward CTRL+↑   Send backward CTRL+↓   Clone selection ALT+drag   Edit/History   Undo last command CTRL+Z   Redo last command CTRL+Y   Cut the selected controls CTRL+X   Copy the selected controls CTRL+C   Paste CTRL+V   Paste In Place CTRL+SHIFT+V   Delete the selected controls DELETE or BACKSPACE   Duplicate the selected controls CTRL+D   Lock the selected controls CTRL+2   Unlock all locked controls CTRL+3   Group   Group the selected controls CTRL+G   Ungroup the selected groups CTRL+SHIFT+G   Align   Align selected controls left CTRL+ALT+1   Align selected controls center CTRL+ALT+2   Align selected controls right CTRL+ALT+3   Align selected controls top CTRL+ALT+4   Align selected controls middle CTRL+ALT+5   Align selected controls bottom CTRL+ALT+6   Working with Icons    Navigating the Suggestion List ↑↓←→   Using the selected icon ENTER   Closing the Icons Library ESC   Closing the Suggestion List ESC   Working with Text    Start Editing text of the selected control ENTER or F2   Committing the current text ENTER (single-line controls), CTRL+ENTER (multi-line controls) or click anywhere   Ignoring the current edit ESC   Grow/Increase Text Size CTRL+]   Shrink/Decrease Text Size CTRL+[   Text Formatting    italic _text in underscores_   link [text in brackets]   link with a target [text in brackets](mockup_name) or [text in brackets](website_url)   bold *text in asterisks*   disabled -text in hyphens-   strikethrough ~text in tildes~   font point size {size:12}text{size}   color (hex value or color name) {color:#ff0000}text{color} or {color:red}text{color}   To type a literal *, , − -, or [] in a control, escape it by prefixing it with a \ (backslash): \*, \, −\-, \, [\]   Special Text Macros    Lorem-Ipsum generator type _lorem_ in a Paragraph or Text Area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keyboard Shortcuts</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/shortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/shortcuts/</guid>
      <description>Below is a list of all the keyboard shortcuts and modifiers available in Balsamiq Mockups 3. While all of the shortcuts will work in the Desktop version, some might not work in our web versions.
The shortcuts below apply to Mockups 3 and higher.
  Working with Controls    Selection   Edit the selected control&amp;#39;s text ENTER or F2   Add to selection SHIFT+CLICK   Toggle selection CTRL+CLICK   Select All CTRL+A   Deselect All CTRL+SHIFT+A   Ignore control(s) under cursor Hold ALT   Treat/do not treat selection as markup CTRL+SHIFT+K   Size/Position   Resize maintaining aspect ratio Hold SHIFT while resizing with mouse   Move selection along horizontal or vertical axis Hold SHIFT while dragging   Disable snapping during move or resize Hold CTRL   Grow/Increase text or icon size CTRL+]   Shrink/Decrease text or icon size CTRL+[   Nudge selection 1px &amp;uarr;&amp;darr;&amp;larr;&amp;rarr;   Nudge selection 10px SHIFT+&amp;uarr;&amp;darr;&amp;larr;&amp;rarr;   Nudge-Resize selection 1px CTRL+ALT+&amp;uarr;&amp;darr;&amp;larr;&amp;rarr;   Nudge-Resize selection 10px CTRL+ALT+SHIFT+&amp;uarr;&amp;darr;&amp;larr;&amp;rarr;   Auto-Size selection CTRL+ALT+0   Pan the canvas (Hand tool) SPACE BAR+Click and Drag   Bring to front CTRL+SHIFT+&amp;uarr;   Send to back CTRL+SHIFT+&amp;darr;   Bring forward CTRL+&amp;uarr;   Send backward CTRL+&amp;darr;   Duplicate selection ALT+drag   Edit/History   Undo last command CTRL+Z   Redo last command CTRL+Y or CTRL+SHIFT+Z   Cut the selected controls CTRL+X or SHIFT+DELETE   Copy the selected controls CTRL+C or CTRL+INSERT   Paste CTRL+V or SHIFT+INSERT   Paste In Place CTRL+SHIFT+V   Delete the selected controls DELETE or BACKSPACE   Duplicate the selected controls CTRL+D   Lock the selected controls CTRL+2   Unlock all locked controls CTRL+3   Transform the selected controls CTRL+T   Group   Group the selected controls CTRL+G   Ungroup the selected groups CTRL+SHIFT+G   Align   Align selected controls left CTRL+ALT+1   Align selected controls center CTRL+ALT+2   Align selected controls right CTRL+ALT+3   Align selected controls top CTRL+ALT+4   Align selected controls middle CTRL+ALT+5   Align selected controls bottom CTRL+ALT+6   Working with Icons    Navigating the Suggestion List &amp;uarr;&amp;darr;&amp;larr;&amp;rarr;   Using the selected icon ENTER   Closing the Icons Library ESC   Closing the Suggestion List ESC   Grow/Increase icon size CTRL+]   Shrink/Decrease icon size CTRL+[   Working with Text    Start Editing text of the selected control ENTER or F2   Committing the current text ENTER (single-line controls), CTRL+ENTER (multi-line controls) or click anywhere   Ignoring the current edit ESC   Grow/Increase Text Size CTRL+]   Shrink/Decrease Text Size CTRL+[   Text Formatting    italic _text in underscores_   link [text in brackets]   link with a target [text in brackets](mockup_name) or</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keyboard Shortcuts</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_wireframes/shortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_wireframes/shortcuts/</guid>
      <description>Below is a list of all the keyboard shortcuts and modifiers available in Balsamiq Wireframes.
Note: Some of these shortcuts do not work in our web versions, depending on which browser and operating system you are using.   Working with Controls    Selection   Edit the selected control&amp;#39;s text ENTER or F2   Add to selection SHIFT+Click   Toggle selection CTRL+Click   Select All CTRL+A   Deselect All CTRL+SHIFT+A   Ignore control(s) under cursor Hold ALT   Treat/do not treat selection as markup CTRL+SHIFT+K   Size/Position   Resize maintaining aspect ratio Hold SHIFT while resizing with mouse   Move selection along horizontal or vertical axis Hold SHIFT while dragging   Disable snapping during move or resize Hold CTRL   Grow/Increase text or icon size CTRL+]   Shrink/Decrease text or icon size CTRL+[   Nudge selection 1px &amp;uarr;&amp;darr;&amp;larr;&amp;rarr;   Nudge selection 10px SHIFT+&amp;uarr;&amp;darr;&amp;larr;&amp;rarr;   Nudge-Resize selection 1px CTRL+ALT+&amp;uarr;&amp;darr;&amp;larr;&amp;rarr;   Nudge-Resize selection 10px CTRL+ALT+SHIFT+&amp;uarr;&amp;darr;&amp;larr;&amp;rarr;   Auto-Size selection CTRL+ALT+0   Pan the canvas (Hand tool) SPACE BAR+Click and drag   Bring to front CTRL+SHIFT+&amp;uarr;   Send to back CTRL+SHIFT+&amp;darr;   Bring forward CTRL+&amp;uarr;   Send backward CTRL+&amp;darr;   Duplicate selection ALT+drag   Edit/History   Undo last command CTRL+Z   Redo last command CTRL+Y or CTRL+SHIFT+Z   Cut the selected controls CTRL+X or SHIFT+DELETE   Copy the selected controls CTRL+C or CTRL+INSERT   Paste CTRL+V or SHIFT+INSERT   Paste In Place CTRL+SHIFT+V   Delete the selected controls DELETE or BACKSPACE   Duplicate the selected controls CTRL+D   Lock the selected controls CTRL+2   Unlock all locked controls CTRL+3   Transform the selected controls CTRL+ALT+T   Group   Group the selected controls CTRL+G   Ungroup the selected groups CTRL+SHIFT+G   Align   Align selected controls left CTRL+ALT+1   Align selected controls center CTRL+ALT+2   Align selected controls right CTRL+ALT+3   Align selected controls top CTRL+ALT+4   Align selected controls middle CTRL+ALT+5   Align selected controls bottom CTRL+ALT+6   Working with Icons    Navigating the Suggestion List &amp;uarr;&amp;darr;&amp;larr;&amp;rarr;   Using the selected icon ENTER   Closing the Icons Library ESC   Closing the Suggestion List ESC   Grow/Increase icon size CTRL+]   Shrink/Decrease icon size CTRL+[   Working with Text    Start Editing text of the selected control ENTER or F2   Committing the current text ENTER (single-line controls), CTRL+ENTER (multi-line controls) or click anywhere   Ignoring the current edit ESC   Grow/Increase Text Size CTRL+]   Shrink/Decrease Text Size CTRL+[   Text Formatting    italic _text in underscores_   link [text in brackets]   link with a target [text in brackets](mockup_name) or</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linking Mockups Together</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b2/linking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b2/linking/</guid>
      <description>You can link mockups together to create a simple prototype for your site or software application. This can be useful for demonstrating click-through prototypes or for usability testing when you&amp;rsquo;re displaying your project in Full Screen Presentation mode or as an exported PDF.
Linking mockups together is as easy as choosing a mockup name from a drop-down menu. Simply click on a control that supports linking (most do, and here&amp;rsquo;s a workaround for those that don&amp;rsquo;t), and you&amp;rsquo;ll see a &amp;ldquo;Link&amp;rdquo; drop-down in the Property Inspector (click the &amp;ldquo;Show Link Inspector&amp;rdquo; link if you don&amp;rsquo;t see it).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linking Mockups Together</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/linking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/linking/</guid>
      <description>You can link mockups together to create a simple prototype for your site or software application. This can be useful for demonstrating click-through prototypes or for usability testing when you&amp;rsquo;re displaying your project in Full Screen Presentation mode or as an exported PDF.
Linking mockups together is as easy as choosing a mockup name from a drop-down menu. Simply click on a control that supports linking (most do, and here&amp;rsquo;s a workaround for those that don&amp;rsquo;t), and you&amp;rsquo;ll see a &amp;ldquo;Link&amp;rdquo; drop-down in the Property Inspector (click the &amp;ldquo;Show Link Inspector&amp;rdquo; link if you don&amp;rsquo;t see it).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linking Wireframes Together</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_wireframes/linking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_wireframes/linking/</guid>
      <description>You can link wireframes together to create a simple prototype for your site or software application. This can be useful for demonstrating click-through prototypes or for usability testing when you&amp;rsquo;re displaying your project in Full Screen Presentation mode or as an exported PDF.
Linking wireframes together is as easy as choosing a wireframe name from a drop-down menu. Simply click on a control that supports linking (most do, and here&amp;rsquo;s a workaround for those that don&amp;rsquo;t), and you&amp;rsquo;ll see a &amp;ldquo;Link&amp;rdquo; drop-down in the Property Inspector (click the &amp;ldquo;Show Link Inspector&amp;rdquo; link if you don&amp;rsquo;t see it).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markup</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_wireframes/markup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_wireframes/markup/</guid>
      <description>Markup is a special kind of component type in the UI Library that is used for adding annotations, comments, and explanatory notes.
Commonly used Markup items include: Arrow / Line, Callout, Sticky Note, Red X, and Curly Braces. The screenshot below shows the Markup button panel selected in the UI Library, and markup items on the page.
Toggling Markup on and Off When you&amp;rsquo;re editing your wireframes, you will sometimes want to see what the wireframe looks like with Markup off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mockups Application Overview</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b2/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b2/overview/</guid>
      <description>Balsamiq Mockups is made up of three major blocks. From top to bottom: the Application Bar, the UI library, and the Mockup Canvas Each is described below.
The Application Bar The application bar includes Menus, the Quick Add tool, and the Toolbar. Each is described below.
The Menus The Mockups menus should be pretty self-explanatory. The only tricky bit is that the Mockup menu contains different items depending on what version of Balsamiq Mockups you are using.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presenting Your Work</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b2/fullscreen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b2/fullscreen/</guid>
      <description>Mockups includes a &amp;ldquo;Full Screen Presentation&amp;rdquo; mode for those times when you need to present your wireframes to other stakeholders.
To enter Full Screen Presentation mode, just click on the full-screen icon in the top-right corner of Mockups, or select &amp;ldquo;Full Screen Presentation&amp;rdquo; from the View menu.
Mockups will expand to take up your whole screen (to eliminate distractions), and your mockup will be centered on the screen.
You will also see three little buttons in the lower-right corner of your screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search Results</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/search/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharing and Reviewing</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_wireframes/sharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_wireframes/sharing/</guid>
      <description>Balsamiq Wireframes is designed for collaboration and offers many ways for you to get feedback on your designs. This document outlines a few different ways so that you can pick the right one to fit each situation.
To learn how to work on the same wireframes together, see our article on Collaborative Editing.
Reviewing and Commenting The &amp;ldquo;Review and Comment&amp;rdquo; mode is a great option for anyone who does not need to edit the wireframes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Symbols</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_wireframes/symbols/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_wireframes/symbols/</guid>
      <description>Balsamiq Wireframes supports the concept of Symbols. A Symbol is a group of controls that represents a single piece of functionality. It is often used for parts of the user interface that show up on several screens. Other software sometimes refers to this feature as templates, master pages, custom components, or widgets.
In essence, Symbols let you create reusable common elements that you can use across different wireframes.
Creating Symbols There are two ways to create a Symbol, described below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Project Info Panel</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/projectinfo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/projectinfo/</guid>
      <description>New in Balsamiq Mockups 3 is the ability to define project-wide settings for skin, font, and link and selection color. The Project Info panel contains these settings as well as an area to add notes about the project. Click the icon next to the Property Inspector icon to toggle the Project Info panel (keyboard shortcut: CTRL/CMD + ,).
These settings will be applied to all mockups in the project and will be saved with the project (i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Property Inspector</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b2/inspector/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b2/inspector/</guid>
      <description>The Property Inspector (also called the toolbox, palette, property dialog, properties window, toolbar, floating window, floating tool bar, properties box and control dialog) is the little floating rectangle that appears once you select one or more UI controls. It allows you to perform some common functions such as copying/pasting, layering, and aligning controls, as well as some control-specific customizations.
The Property Inspector is displayed when you select an object on the canvas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Property Inspector</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/inspector/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/inspector/</guid>
      <description>The Property Inspector is a panel on the right side of the application that allows you to set some common properties such as alignment, position and size as well as settings specific to certain controls (selection state, text properties, color, etc.). It is available when viewing mockups, assets, and Symbols.
You can show and hide the Property Inspector by clicking the toggle icon above it (keyboard shortcut CTRL/CMD + ; or ALT/Option + Enter).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Images, Assets, and Icons</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_wireframes/images/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_wireframes/images/</guid>
      <description>There are multiple ways to add images and icons to your wireframes. The easiest way is to simply drag and drop an image file from your computer on to the wireframes canvas. Read on to learn more about adding and using images, icons, and other assets to your projects.
Adding Images in Wireframes View As mentioned above, dragging an image from your computer to the editor will add it to the canvas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Alternates</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/alternates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/alternates/</guid>
      <description>Alternates (also sometimes referred to as versions or branches) allow you to create variations on a single mockup design without adding more mockups to your project.
Creating alternates can be useful during the early design phase when exploring concepts and in later stages for reviewers to add their feedback and propose changes.
Some possible reasons for using alternates:
 You want to create only one mockup per screen but have several ideas about each one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Data Grids / Tables</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b2/datagrids/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b2/datagrids/</guid>
      <description>The Data Grid control functions like many other text-based controls. It uses commas as column separators and new lines as rows. A basic table with three columns and two rows would look like this:
First Name, Last Name, Email Address firstname, lastname, email@email.com  You can choose whether to show the first row as a header row in the Property Inspector, as well as specifying the row height, row colors, and grid lines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Data Grids / Tables</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/datagrids/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/datagrids/</guid>
      <description>The Data Grid control functions like many other text-based controls. It uses commas as column separators and new lines as rows. A basic table with three columns and two rows would look like this:
First Name, Last Name, Email Address firstname, lastname, email@email.com  You can choose whether to show the first row as a header row in the Property Inspector, as well as specifying the row height, row colors, and grid lines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Icons</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b2/icons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b2/icons/</guid>
      <description>Balsamiq Mockups and myBalsamiq come packed with over 600 icons courtesy of the Font Awesome Icon Library.
There are two ways to select an icon to use: the icon search and the icon library.
Icon Search If the controls you selected support icons, you will see the icon search box in the property inspector. This works much like the Quick Add tool: just type a few letters from the name of the icon you are looking for and a list of suggestions will pop up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Icons</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/icons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/icons/</guid>
      <description>Balsamiq Mockups 3 includes the amazing Font Awesome icon set. It contains over 500 icons in a wide range of categories that can be sized from very small to very large. It is also updated frequently and we plan to keep up with the updates whenever we release a new version of our product (more about why we switched here).
It should meet all your icon needs, but if not, you can add your own icons or request new ones from Font Awesome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Images</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b2/images/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b2/images/</guid>
      <description>Adding Images To use images in Mockups, add an Image control from the UI Library and place it on the canvas. The Image drop-down in the Property Inspector will allow you to select images that have already been imported/used in your mockup or import a new one.
The Project Assets panel shows all images in your assets. If you have Site/Account assets, a tab will appear for them. If you use web images or images using relative paths that are not project assets, those will show in the Other Assets tab.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Images and Assets</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/images/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/images/</guid>
      <description>There are multiple ways to add images to your mockups. The easiest way is to simply drag and drop an image file from your computer on to the Mockups canvas. Read on to learn more about adding and using images and other assets in your projects.
Adding Images in Mockups View As mentioned above, dragging an image from your computer to Balsamiq Mockups will add it to the canvas. Doing this will place the image into the selected mockup and copy the image file to your Assets so that you can easily reuse it in other mockups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Markup</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b2/markup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b2/markup/</guid>
      <description>Markup is a special kind of component in the UI Library that is used for adding annotations, comments, and explanatory notes.
Commonly used Markup items include: Arrow / Line, Callout, Sticky Note, Red X, and Curly Braces. The screenshot below shows the Markup button panel selected in the UI Library, and markup items on the page.
Toggling Markup on and Off When you&amp;rsquo;re editing your mockups, you will sometimes want to see what the mockup looks like with Markup off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Markup</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/markup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/markup/</guid>
      <description>Markup is a special kind of component in the UI Library that is used for adding annotations, comments, and explanatory notes.
Commonly used Markup items include: Arrow / Line, Callout, Sticky Note, Red X, and Curly Braces. The screenshot below shows the Markup button panel selected in the UI Library, and markup items on the page.
Toggling Markup on and Off When you&amp;rsquo;re editing your mockups, you will sometimes want to see what the mockup looks like with Markup off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Site Maps</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b2/sitemaps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b2/sitemaps/</guid>
      <description>You can create simple site maps from a text outline using the Site Map control.
Create a Site Map Add a &amp;ldquo;Site Map&amp;rdquo; control from the UI Library to the canvas.
Edit the control by double-clicking or selecting it and pressing the Enter key. Edit the outline to create parent-child relationships. Each line represents a box (or page/node) in your sitemap. Use hyphens to indent child boxes beneath a parent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Site Maps</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/sitemaps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/sitemaps/</guid>
      <description>You can create simple site maps from a text outline using the Site Map control.
Create a Site Map Add a &amp;ldquo;Site Map&amp;rdquo; control from the UI Library to the canvas.
Edit the control by double-clicking or selecting it and pressing the Enter key. Edit the outline to create parent-child relationships. Each line represents a box (or page/node) in your sitemap. Use hyphens to indent child boxes beneath a parent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Skins (Sketch vs. Wireframe)</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b2/skins/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b2/skins/</guid>
      <description>We know that some people need to shift from idea generation with internal teams to presentation with clients or stakeholders, and in those situations the default &amp;ldquo;sketch&amp;rdquo; skin may present challenges with certain audiences. To address this need, we created a &amp;ldquo;wireframe&amp;rdquo; skin that allows you to switch from a sketchy, hand-drawn style to a crisper, cleaner wireframe elements.
Switching from Sketch to Wireframe Skin To switch skins go to the View menu, select the Skin from the dropdown, and set the Skin setting to &amp;ldquo;Wireframe&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Skins (Sketch vs. Wireframe)</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/skins/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/skins/</guid>
      <description>We know that some people need to shift from idea generation with internal teams to presentation with clients or stakeholders, and in those situations the default &amp;ldquo;sketch&amp;rdquo; skin may present challenges with certain audiences. To address this need, we created a &amp;ldquo;wireframe&amp;rdquo; skin that allows you to switch from a sketchy, hand-drawn style to a crisper, cleaner wireframe elements.
Switching from Sketch to Wireframe Skin To switch skins go to the Project Info panel and set the Skin setting to &amp;ldquo;Wireframe&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Text</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b2/text/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b2/text/</guid>
      <description>Many Mockups UI controls, such as Button, Label or DataGrid, have text in them. To edit the text, double-click on the control and start typing. Or, if you have the control selected, simply hit Enter or F2 to start editing. To commit the text you typed, simply click anywhere other than the text field you typed in or hit Enter or CTRL+Enter. If you want to discard the text changes you just made, hit the ESC key.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Text</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/text/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/text/</guid>
      <description>Many Mockups UI controls, such as Button, Label or DataGrid, have text in them. To edit the text, double-click on the control and start typing. Or, if you have the control selected, simply hit Enter or F2 to start editing. To commit the text you typed, simply click anywhere other than the text field you typed in or hit Enter or CTRL+Enter. If you want to discard the text changes you just made, hit the ESC key.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with UI Controls</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b2/controls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b2/controls/</guid>
      <description>Adding UI Controls To add new UI controls to your mockup, you can use the UI Library or type a keyword into the Quick Add tool.
You can also duplicate controls already on the canvas using copy and paste or the duplicate command (CTRL/CMD + D).
Note: Full list of keyboard shortcuts here. Selecting UI Controls There are a few different ways to select UI controls. If you are familiar with graphics software, these should be of no surprise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with UI Controls</title>
      <link>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/controls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmclssg1.github.io/ssdocs/_editor/_b3/controls/</guid>
      <description>Adding UI Controls To add UI controls to your mockup, double-click or drag a control in the UI Library or type a keyword into the Quick Add tool.
You can also duplicate controls already on the canvas using copy and paste or the duplicate command (CTRL/CMD + D). ALT/Option + drag will also duplicate controls and allow you to place them using your mouse.
Note: Full list of keyboard shortcuts here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>